<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>lithiyum</title>
	<atom:link href="http://lithiyum.me/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://lithiyum.me</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 13:44:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title></title>
		<link>http://lithiyum.me/2021/12/26/best-android-apps-i-have-used/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lithiyum]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://lithiyum.me/?p=111</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Best Android Apps I Have Used The best Android apps include a social media giant, a video editor and a game streaming service. Tik Tok TikTok is a social video app that allows you to make short movies while lip-syncing, dancing to tunes, or talking about something you&#8217;re passionate about. During the early months of &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="http://lithiyum.me/2021/12/26/best-android-apps-i-have-used/">  Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Best Android Apps I Have Used</h2>
<p>The best Android apps include a social media giant, a video editor and a game streaming service.</p>
<p><img title="Apps2" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/elementor/thumbs/Apps2-pi3140oahhgk13e06lhsze9ud228m098kij7av1a0w.jpg" alt="Apps2" /></p>
<h2>Tik Tok</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/merlin_193626909_b852af39-4c3e-4467-b0bb-0e5cf87bd1f2-articleLarge.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/merlin_193626909_b852af39-4c3e-4467-b0bb-0e5cf87bd1f2-articleLarge.jpg 600w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/merlin_193626909_b852af39-4c3e-4467-b0bb-0e5cf87bd1f2-articleLarge-300x200.jpg 300w" alt="" width="600" height="400" /></p>
<p>TikTok is a social video app that allows you to make short movies while lip-syncing, dancing to tunes, or talking about something you&#8217;re passionate about. During the early months of the epidemic in 2020, the app&#8217;s popularity skyrocketed, with more than 2 billion downloads across the App Store and Google Play. According to Sensor Tower data, TikTok generated 315 million installs in the first quarter of 2020, the highest for any app in a quarter ever.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s worth noting that TikTok has being scrutinized by the US government for potential security dangers and privacy violations. The app was recently questioned by the US Senate on the safety of its younger users. Additional legislation to safeguard younger users could result from the hearing.</p>
<p>TikTok is available for free on the Google Play store. It&#8217;s also available on iPhone and iPad.</p>
<h2>Telegram</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1200x630wa-768x403.png" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1200x630wa-768x403.png 768w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1200x630wa-300x158.png 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1200x630wa-1024x538.png 1024w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1200x630wa.png 1200w" alt="" width="768" height="403" /></p>
<p>Telegram is one of the most popular privacy-focused messaging programs. It has symmetrical AES encryption of 256 bits, 2048-bit RSA encryption, and more. As a result, it is one of the safest messaging systems available. File sharing, cross-platform support, group conversations, GIF support, and more are all included in the app. It&#8217;s one of the best security systems, and it&#8217;s private enough that some governments don&#8217;t want their citizens to use it. It&#8217;s more than adequate as a chat service for just about anything you would require.</p>
<h2>Stadia</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Stadia_03_19_19-768x432.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Stadia_03_19_19-768x432.jpg 768w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Stadia_03_19_19-300x169.jpg 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Stadia_03_19_19-1024x576.jpg 1024w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/Stadia_03_19_19.jpg 1400w" alt="" width="768" height="432" /></p>
<p>Stadia, Google&#8217;s video game streaming service, allows you to play games on your phone, laptop, desktop, or television. The Stadia app serves as a hub for managing your Stadia account, configuring your controller, making purchases, reviewing your captures, and playing games (depending on your phone). While the service has received mixed reviews, the app has received a 3.7 out of 5 star rating in the Google Play store from over 25,000 users.</p>
<p>The Google Stadia software is free to download from the Play Store, but games and the package to connect to it are not.</p>
<h2>Call of Duty:Mobile</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv-768x432.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv-768x432.jpg 768w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv-300x169.jpg 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv-1024x576.jpg 1024w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv-1536x864.jpg 1536w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/main-kv.jpg 1920w" alt="" width="768" height="432" /></p>
<p>According to Statista, in the first two months after its debut, Call of Duty: Mobile had 172 million downloads globally. The United States accounted for about 28.5 million of the downloads. While publisher Activision Blizzard had some issues with the mobile edition of the famous first-person shooter game, those issues appear to have been rectified, and users are still downloading the game.</p>
<p>In the Google Play store, Call of Duty: Mobile has over 14 million reviews and a rating of 4.3 out of 5 stars. Call of Duty: Mobile is available for free in the Google Play store, with optional in-game purchases. It&#8217;s also available on iPhone and iPad.</p>
<h2>Disney Plus</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/db9d73ec-2c53-4827-bdd6-74b9f02e44d6.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 560px) 100vw, 560px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/db9d73ec-2c53-4827-bdd6-74b9f02e44d6.jpg 560w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/db9d73ec-2c53-4827-bdd6-74b9f02e44d6-300x200.jpg 300w" alt="" width="560" height="373" /></p>
<p>Disney Plus, the streaming service, has maintained its momentum in 2020, winning the Play Store Users&#8217; Choice App award. Disney classics, as well as Star Wars, Marvel, Pixar, and the Simpsons, are among the films and TV shows available on the platform. Disney has already made several improvements to the streaming experience, such as the addition of a resume option.</p>
<p>Disney Plus is available for $8 per month or $80 per year. For $14 per month, you can get Disney Plus, Hulu with Ads, and ESPN Plus, or $20 for Hulu without Ads. The app is available for Android and iOS.</p>
<h2>Google Maps</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/975626gmp-768x493.png" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/975626gmp-768x493.png 768w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/975626gmp-300x193.png 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/975626gmp.png 975w" alt="" width="768" height="493" /></p>
<p>According to Statista, Google Maps has become one of the most popular apps in the United States in terms of audience reach. Incognito mode, a speedometer, traffic incident reporting, and speed trap reporting are all included in the app, making it even more useful (and competitive with Google&#8217;s other navigation app, Waze). And new features are added on a regular basis to assist users see when a site is the most congested or to find a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.</p>
<h2>Ablo</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/493dd05e-0a9b-473d-9730-64fb52970e82.png" sizes="(max-width: 776px) 100vw, 776px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/493dd05e-0a9b-473d-9730-64fb52970e82.png 776w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/493dd05e-0a9b-473d-9730-64fb52970e82-300x152.png 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/493dd05e-0a9b-473d-9730-64fb52970e82-768x388.png 768w" alt="" width="776" height="392" /></p>
<p>Ablo is a communication software that links you with random individuals all over the world and instantly translates your chats and video calls, with the objective of assisting you in learning about another culture, practicing a language, or connecting with people to travel with around the world. Ablo may appear to be a clone of the well-known Chatroulette; however, it has more regulations, and violators are removed off the program.</p>
<p>According to its Play store page, Ablo has received over 10 million downloads and has received a 3.8 out of 5 star rating from over 525,000 users. Ablo is available for free in the Google Play store.</p>
<h2>Duolingo</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/google-invests-duolingo-get-news-1200x900-1-768x576.jpg" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" srcset="http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/google-invests-duolingo-get-news-1200x900-1-768x576.jpg 768w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/google-invests-duolingo-get-news-1200x900-1-300x225.jpg 300w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/google-invests-duolingo-get-news-1200x900-1-1024x768.jpg 1024w, http://lithiyum.me/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/google-invests-duolingo-get-news-1200x900-1.jpg 1200w" alt="" width="768" height="576" /></p>
<p>Duolingo makes learning a second, or even a third, language enjoyable. There are 39 languages available in the app, ranging from Spanish and French to Diné (Navajo). Reading, writing, speaking, and listening tasks are included in the gamified classes, as well as rewards for completing each one. There are also forums where you may vent your frustrations about conjugations to other people learning the same language as you, much like in a real classroom.</p>
<p>In the Google Play store, Duolingo has about 12 million reviews, with an average rating of 4.5 stars out of 5. Duolingo is free to download, but you can upgrade to Duolingo Plus for $13 per month or $84 per year, which works out to $7 per month.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>http://lithiyum.me/2021/12/16/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>http://lithiyum.me/2021/12/16/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[lithiyum]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 14:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http:/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://lithiyum.me/2021/12/16/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
